<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stay-Fit RPG</string>
    <string name="footer">Created by Edward Costache</string>

    <string name="warm_up_recommended">

        NOTE: Before starting any exercise it is recommended that you do at least 5 minutes of warming up, and  drink plenty of water before the exercise, during the breaks and after exercise.

    </string>

    <string name="pushup_description">

        Pushups are a great exercise for working out your upper body and arm muscles. Muscles affected;\n\t
        • Deltoids (Shoulders), Triceps and Biceps which are located on your arms\n\t• Pectorals and Abdominal muscles which
        are located on your chest and stomach.

    </string>
    <string name="pushup_instructions">

        Place your device on the floor with the screen facing up. Position yourself in a pushup position, with your head
        above the phone. Once clicking START do the usual pushup maneuver, but make sure to touch the phone with your chin, or nose
        as you lower yourself.

    </string>
    <string name="situp_description">

        Situps focus on increasing the strength of your abdominal muscles. Muscles affected;\n\t
        • Abdominal muscles located on your stomach.

    </string>
    <string name="situp_instructions">

        Get into a situp position and either hold your phone on your chest, or place your hands behind your head while holding the phone in your hands hand.
        Before you press START make sure you are already laying on the ground. Once you have started the exercise, you can do your sit, the phone will let you know with a sound
        that you have completed one situp. The phone will eventually vibrate, this indicates you have completed the round, and you can take a break, or the exercise is over.

    </string>
    <string name="running_description">

        Running is a great activity for building leg muscles and increasing your stamina and general fitness. Muscles affected;\n\t
        • Soleus, located on the side of your ankles, also known as inner calf muscles.\n\t
        • Gastrocnemius, located behind the shin bone, also known as calves.\n\t
        • Quadriceps, located on the front on your leg.\n\t
        • Hamstrings, located behind the Quadriceps, on the back of your leg.

    </string>
    <string name="running_instructions">

        NOTE: Make sure you do not look at the phone will running to not hurt yourself.
        When running, you will need to reach the required speed in order for the distance you need to reach to decrease. You will be given a distance goal, that you need to reach while running at a certain speed or higher
        , the application will let you know if you need to run faster by making the phone vibrate. Once you have reached the goal, the phone will vibrate twice and make a sound to let you know you can take a break.

    </string>
    <string name="squat_description">

        Squats are solely used to massively increase the power in your legs and hips. Muscles affected;\n\t
        • Quadriceps, located on the front on your leg.\n\t
        • Hamstrings, located behind the Quadriceps, on the back of your leg.\n\t
        • Glutes, located on the back of your hips, the bum cheeks.\n\t
        • Gastrocnemius, located behind the shin bone, also known as calves.

    </string>
    <string name="squat_instructions">

        When doing squats, hold your phone in front of you and proceed to do a normal squat by lowering yourself down while keeping your legs in the same position and bending your knees. You can look at your phone while doing squats
        to see how many squats you have left until a break.

    </string>
    <string name="break_instructions">

        DRINK SOME WATER!\nWater is very important when doing exercise, because your body constantly sweats dehydrating your body. It is vital to rehydrate during breaks, and after exercise.\n\n
        GET YOUR BREATH BACK!\nYour body uses oxygen to fuel your muscles with energy, make sure you take deep breaths during breaks.

    </string>
    <string name="verion_code">V0.2</string>
</resources>